Good morning, ma'am.
What's your job today?
I'm here on a job for a heavy worker.
I'm here at Mobility Dote Motegi.
The scenery is a bit nice.
It's really nice to feel the autumn.
I thought autumn was over.
I'm so happy to be able to feel the autumn
I'm so happy!
I'm looking forward to it!
I want to go in, I want to go in!
It feels like a circuit.
I want to go ziplining.
I'm looking forward to it
I'm looking forward to having fun with you.
See you soon.
Here we are!
Perfect day for ziplining!
What's a zipline, by the way?
Zipline.
A wire is attached like this
Attached to it
A walk in the air
It's an experience where you can take a walk in the sky.
It's not so easy to do.
I think you need a big place to do it.
It's a big place, isn't it?
Take a walk while feeling the nature.
Go for a walk in the sky
I'm off.
I'm Hotta.
I'm fully equipped.
321.
I'm off!
bleiben
Wow! Is it a lot of climbing?
But if I get down like this, I won't be able to do the show, so I won't be able to get through the tour.
Don't be bummed out. Oh, my gosh! It's acorn-ish.
Acorns?
One acorn.
Oh, no!
I'm in!
Oh! At last!
Taran!
He's in!
Ah, electric warriors!
One by one.
I'll go once. What if I go s'mores?
It's not a test.
Oh, oh!
Yes, I'm going!
Yes, yes, yes, I'm going.
Three, two, one.
I'm in!
Wow!
That's great! Oh, my God, I'm definitely getting a feel for it.
One at a time. One at a time.
Who's going first?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors to see who wins.
Okay, first one goes goo, rock, paper, scissors, bye!
I got it. I got it.
I'll go first!
You got it.
I love this kind of thing.
That's why I'm glad. I'm the kind of person who doesn't get this kind of stimulation on a regular basis.
It makes me happy.
Makes me want to give my heart to you.
Thank you very much.
You mean the return maneuver?
Yes, sir.
Give me your heart.
Oh, no!
Come on!
Whoo! Off you go!
Oh!
They're yelling!
Oh, my God!
I think it's one of ours.
Let's level!
I'm waiting for Fukuoka!
Sorry, we're at the top of the list!
Well, Rikkun went, didn't he?
Okay, I'll go now.
Okay, next one, please...
I'll give my heart, everyone!
Here we go!
Gan-chan!
Go!
Yes!
JR East E233 series train
Thank you for your hard work.
Yes, I'm going to step back a bit.
Did you have a good time? It was fun.
It felt really good.
I was most scared at the end when I had to brake.
The leader is coming now, so I would love to see the moment of the leader's braking.
Yes, please do. Tsubasa. Here I go.
Wow, great. Rico, wait for me.
Here we go. Countdown, 3, 2, 1, GO!
I'm off! Wow.
Here we are!
Yes, we're here.
Let's back up a little bit.
Yes, I just finished riding the zipline.
It was a lot of fun.
It felt so good, you know what I mean?
I could feel the wind in the air.
It's not often that you can feel nature with your whole body, so I really feel like I've been reborn.
I feel like my luck went up a lot.
It was a lot of fun. I want to do it again.
I want to do it again!
Yes, I do!
So next up, we come to the heart pounding, bone rubbing check for the mind's eye!
Hey!
This is a check I've been wanting to do from afar, so I'm really looking forward to it. Doki-doki.
We can go together on this one, right?
Yes! I'm sure we can do it together this time, so we'll join forces and do our best with a lot of excitement!
Thanks for all your hard work, everyone.
Oh, Ben and his friends are bugs. I'm a bug now, I am.
Euler.
Press longhorned beetle.
Eiler.
Stag beetle. Monarch beetle. Uh, zo, zo, zo.
Wait!
Wait for this! It's impossible!
The big guys look okay.
Can you move?
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
What? What?
How do we get there?
You put your back and your legs like this...
Both back and legs like this.
I can't resist!
Riko's still here.
Riko!
Aah!
I can't do this!
You should see it. One look?
No, I can't do this, I can't do this, I can't do this!
No!
What do I do? Riko!
Riko! What do I do? Riko!
Is this a wall? Is it a wall?
A wall. A wall.
No!
Ha-ha-ha!
I wanna climb it! I want to climb!
Whoa! Riko!
Riko!
Police! I can't!
What?
Aah!
I've calmed down.
I give up!
Huh!
Oh, oh!
Eh, I can't.
I'll get back on my feet.
Yes!
Whoo!
Let's go!
Hang in there!
Ready!
Whoo!
Ooh!
imi
иф
Oh, here they come.
Okay, I'm done pounding.
I'm really excited.
What's next?
I don't know what's coming next.
I didn't know if it was going to be there.
It was harder than I thought it would be
I had to climb by myself.
but it was a lot of fun.
It was a lot of fun.
I hope I will be able to clear all of them.
And there were a lot of kids there, too.
It was a lot of fun!
I hope I made friends with them.
It was a lot of fun.
I'll go again.
Well, it's sad to say that it's already over...
I can't wait to see how fast it goes by.
I really had a lot of fun at Mobility Resort Motegi today.
It's really not enough!
There are so many activities that you have to come back again and again.
I want to do more!
It's great to be able to do it while looking at this view.
It's not often that you get a chance to absorb so much of nature.
I can feel the nature and I can move my body, it's so much fun.
I want to come again.
I want to come back again.
I heard that the stars are beautiful at night.
We have everything here, so please come and visit us at Mobility Resort Motegi!
So, since Highway Walker's article has already been published, here's the URL.
Here is the URL
Please take a look!